Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Administrative, 1975-1990, undated; 1
  - Requests, 1977-1986; 5
    - Patent Gazette, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, Autographed, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Photographs, Autographed, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, Official, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, Official, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Photographs, Official, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Publications, General, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Publications, General, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Publications, General, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Publications, General, 1979-1981, 1983-1985 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Presidential Campaign 1976, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Questionnaires, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Questionnaires, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Soil Surveys, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Soil Surveys, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Soil Surveys, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Texas Legislative Handbook, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Tour, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Tour, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Tour (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Tour (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Tribute Books, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - US Code, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - US Constitution, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - US Government Material, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - US Treaties and Other International Agreements, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - White House Tour Passes, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - White House Tour Passes, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - White House Tour Passes, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Schedules, 1979-1987; 6
    - August Recess, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - August Recess, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Activities, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Congressional Schedules, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Congressman’s Fall Schedule, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Easter Recess, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Easter Recess, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Easter Schedule, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - July Visit, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Leath Schedules, 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Leath Schedules, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Leath Schedules, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Leath Schedules, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Leath Schedules, 1979-1981 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Leath Schedules, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Leath Schedules, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - May Visit, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Rio Airways Schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Staff Travel, 1981 October (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Texas, 1982 January 11-24 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Finances, 1979-1989; 7
    - Quarterly Reports, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Official Expenses, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1979 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 January (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 January 31-February 23 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 February 26-March 30 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 April (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 April 30-May 25 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 May 28-June 29 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 July (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 July 30-August 31 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 September (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 October (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 October 29-November 30 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 December (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Reports, 1979 December 17-1980 January 25 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Official Expenses, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 January 28-February 29 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 March (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 March 31-April 25 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 May (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 June (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 June 30-July 25 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 July 28-August 29 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 September (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 September 29-October 31 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 November (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1980 December (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Official Expenses, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1981 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Reports (W.R.), 1981 January (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 February (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 March (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 March 30-April 24 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 April 27-May 1981 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 June (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 June 29-July 31 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 August (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 August 31-September 28 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 September 28-October 30 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 November (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Weekly Reports, 1981 December (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Official Expenses, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1982 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 January (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 February (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 March (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 April (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 May (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 June (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 July (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 August (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 September (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 October (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 November (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Reports, 1982 December (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Official Expenses, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1983 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 January (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 February (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 March (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 April (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 May (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 June (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 July (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 August (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 September (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 October (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 November (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Reports, 1983 December (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Official Expenses, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1984 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 January (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 January 30-February 24 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 February 27-March 30 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 April (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 April 31-May 25 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 May 1-June 29 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 July (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 July 31-August 31 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 September (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 October (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 October 29-November 30 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Weekly Reports, 1984 December 16-1985 January 4 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Official Expenses, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1985 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 January (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 January 28-February 22 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 February 25- March 29 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 April (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 April 29-May 31 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 June (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 July (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 July 29-August 30 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 September (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 September 30-October 25 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 November (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Weekly Reports, 1985 December (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Official Expenses, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1986 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 January (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 February (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 March (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 March 31-April 18 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 April 21-May 30 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 June (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 June 30-July 31 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 August (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 August 25-September 26 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 September 29-October 31 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 November (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Weekly Reports, 1986 December 1-1986 January 2 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Official Expenses, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1987 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Official Expenses, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1988 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Reports, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Official Expenses, 1989 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Official Expenses (Work Copy), 1989 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 0-99, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 100-199, 1979-1980 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 200-299, 1980-1981 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 300-399, 1981-1983 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 400-499, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 500-599, 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 600-699, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Official Expenses Vouchers, 700-799, 1987-1989 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Employment, 1979-1981; 8
    - General, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - General, Internships, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - General, Internships, LBJ, 1978-1979 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Agencies, 1978-1981; 2
  This smaller series reflects the broad array of government agencies that contacted Leath from 1978-1980. Typical entries include Amtrak, the EPA, and Texas Department of Agriculture. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - ACTION, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Council for Technical Vocational Education, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - American Bank of Waco, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - American Educational Complex Consortium (Con.), Texas (TX), 1979 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1979 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Amtrak, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Amtrak, General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Amtrak, Texas & Arkansas Correspondence, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Attorney General, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Balanced Budget Caucus, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Blue Cross — Blue Shield, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Brazos River Authority, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Central Texas Council of Governments, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Central Texas Economic Development District, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Central Texas Health Systems Agency, Incorporated (Inc.), 1979 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Central Texas Planned Parenthood Association, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Central Texas Planned Parenthood Association, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Civil Rights, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Commission on Alcoholism, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Community Services Administration, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Congressional Clearinghouse on the Future, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Congressional Clearinghouse on Women’s Rights, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Congressional Club, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Coal Caucus, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Congressional Hispanic Caucus, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Congressional Textile Caucus, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Tourism Caucus, 1979-1980 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Conservative Caucus, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Consumer Product Safety Commission (CPSC), 1979 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Council of Governments Directory, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Council on Environmental Quality, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Council on Wage and Price Stability, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Democratic Caucus, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Democratic Party of Texas, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Democratic Research Organization, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Democratic Research Organization, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Democratic Study Group, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Democratic Study Group, Daily Report, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Democratic Study Group, Fact Sheet, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Democratic Study Group, Legislative Report, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Democratic Study Group, Special Report, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Democratic Study Group, Staff Bulletin, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Department of Agriculture, Texas Extension Service, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Economic Development Agency (EDA), 1979 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, Agent Orange, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, Railroad Noise Regulation, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Export-Import Bank, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Federal Communications Commission (FCC), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - FCC, Frank Mayborn, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - FCC, New Station Applications, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Federal Elections Commission (FEC), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank Board, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Federal Reserve System, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1979 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Federal Trade Commission, Used Car Sales, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Former Members of Congress, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Forum on Regulations, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Governor’s Conference on Handicapped Individuals, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - General Services Administration (GSA), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - House of Representatives, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - House of Representatives, Committees on Regions, Compacts, and Districts, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, News and Memorandums, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, Trucking Regulation, EP 135, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Interagency Task Force on Ionizing Radiation, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Joint Committee to Study Long-Term Care Alternatives, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Marlin Chamber of Commerce, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - National Archives, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - National Commission on Digestive Diseases, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - National Commission on the International Year of the Child, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH), 1979 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - New Members Caucus, 96th, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Regulatory Commission, Comanche Peak, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Office of Personnel Management, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Office of Secretary of State of Texas, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Office of State-Federal Relations, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Office of the Governor, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Ozarks Regional Commission, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Pecan Valley Economic Development District, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Postal Service, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Postal Service, Energy, TX, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Railroad Commission of Texas, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Railroad Retirement Board, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Republican Study Committee, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - San Saba County Property Owners Association, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Securities & Exchange Commission (SEC), 1979 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Small Business Administration (SBA), 1979 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Smithsonian, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Southwest Federal Regional Council, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Staff, Congressional Staff Journal, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - State Bar of Texas, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - State Board of Higher Education, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - State Board of Insurance, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - State Department of Highways and Public Transportation, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - State Fuel Allocation Office, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - State Senate of Texas, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Strategy Council on Drug Abuse, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Surplus Property Agency, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (TVA), 1979 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Texas & Southwestern Cattle Raiser’s Association, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Texas Adult Agency, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Texas Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Texas Air Control Board, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Texas Alcoholic Beverage Commission, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Texas Association of Broadcasters, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Texas Association of Life Underwriters, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Texas Chamber of Commerce Executives (Exec.), 1979 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Texas Committee for the Humanities, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Texas Council of Child Welfare Boards, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Texas Deepwater Port Authority, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Texas Democratic Delegation, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Texas Department of Human Resources, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Texas Department of Agriculture, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Texas Department of Health, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Texas Education Agency, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Texas Employment Commission, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Texas Energy Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Texas Farm Bureau, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Texas Farmers Union, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Texas Hospital Association, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Texas Hydraulics, Inc., 1979 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Texas Industrial Commission, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Texas Institute for Medical Assessment, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Texas Jaycees, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Texas Mapping Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Texas Mid-Continent Oil and Gas Association, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Texas Parks and Wildlife Department, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Texas Pharmaceutical Association, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Texas Power and Light, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Texas Railroad Association, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Texas Savings and Loan Department, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Texas School Food Service Association, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Texas Soil and Water Conversation, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Texas State Commission for the Blind, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Texas State Society, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Texas State Teacher’s Association, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Texas Statewide Health Coordination Council, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Texas Tax Reform Immediately (TRIM), 1979 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Texas Tourist Development Agency, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Texas Utilities Commission, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Texas Water Commission, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Texas-New Mexico Sugar Beet Growers, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - The Advisory Council for Technical Vocational Education in Texas, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - The Texas AggieDLTexas A&M Alumni, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Tourist Development Agency, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Texas Council of Child Welfare Boards, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Texas Department of Community Affairs, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Texas Department of Corrections, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - United Nations, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - United States (US) Metric Board, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Veterans Administration (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Veterans Administration (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Veterans Administration, 11th District Construction Projects, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Veterans Administration, Medical Facilities, 11th District, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Veterans Service Offices Directory, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Water Resources, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - West Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Women’s Political Caucus, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - World Bank, International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1978-1990, undated; 3
  This lengthy series spanning 1979-1990 includes five subseries: 1. General, 2. Incoming, 3. Outgoing, 4. Replies, and 5. Master Directory. The first and third subseries are in chronological order while the others reflect alphabetic arrangement. Additionally, the Replies subseries is topically arranged. The bulk of this series consists of letters to and from constituents and other members of Congress. The Master Directory subseries is missing correspondence from names beginning G-I.
  - General, 1981-1990; 1
    - December, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - January (1 of 10), 1982 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - January (2 of 10), 1982 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - January (3 of 10), 1982 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - January (4 of 10), 1982 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - January (5 of 10), 1982 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - January (6 of 10), 1982 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - January (7 of 10), 1982 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - January (8 of 10), 1982 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - January (9 of 10), 1982 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - January (10 of 10), 1982 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - February (1 of 20), 1982 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - February (2 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - February (3 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - February (4 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - February (5 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - February (6 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - February (7 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - February (8 of 20), 1982 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - February (9 of 20), 1982 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - February (10 of 20), 1982 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - February (11 of 20), 1982 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - February (12 of 20), 1982 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - February (13 of 20), 1982 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - February (14 of 20), 1982 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - February (15 of 20), 1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - February (16 of 20), 1982 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - February (17 of 20), 1982 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - February (18 of 20), 1982 (Box 70, Folder 5)